RambodRahmani

Student at University of Pisa

Contact

Via Pietro Casu, 16 Sassari, (SS) 07100 Italy

(+39) 333 3840979 (+39) 079 2859049

rambodrahmani@yahoo.it rambodrahmani.it

Languages

Persian (Mother tongue) Italian (Mother tongue) English (C1) French (A2) Spanish (A1)

Programming •

Java, JavaFX, Python, C, C++, Objective-C, .NET Framework, R, Latex, OpenCV, APEX, SQL, PL/SQL, MySQL, PHP, CSS, JavaScript, iQuery, HTML5, Django, XML, GWT, JSON, Shell Script.

Software

xCode, Android Studio, Windows Phone SDK, Matlab, Visual Studio, Eclipse, Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Premiere Pro, VirtualBox, , ISPConfig, Openstack, Puppet, OpenMediaVault, MongoDB, Metasploit, Wireshark, Git, Jira, Trac.

Hardware

Arduino, Raspberry Pi, Embedded Pi, Cubieboard, Torobot, TP-Link CPE210, CPE510, EAP225, Ubiquiti Nanostation M3 and Picostation.

Summary

I was born in Iran in 1993 and moved to Italy at the age of 7. I started studying programming languages at the age of 15 and began to work as a freelance programmer a couple of years later. At the age of 19 I was admitted at the University of Pisa as a Computer Science Student and I am currently studying for my last exams. In the last four years, beside studying for my examinations, I worked for IT Companies and for the Italian government, I took part in group projects and tried to startup my own ideas. During the academic year 2016/2017, my goals have shifted. I have developed a deep interest in Quantum Physics and its applications to computer science: I am hoping to pursue an academic career in Quantum Computer Science.

Education

2013 - 2017 **Bachelor** of Engineering Studies - Computer Science University of Pisa, Italy 2008 - 2013 High School Diploma 100/100 - Scientific Lyceum Scientific Lyceum "G. Spano", Italy

Personal Studies

The following is a list of in-depth courses which I followed during my Bachelor of Engineering.

Complete Java Masterclass: Learn to master Java 8 core development.

Learning JavaFX GUI Development: Develop enterprise apps using JavaFX.

Python 3 and Django Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp.

Advanced C++ Programming: Intermediate to advanced C++, including C++ 11's additions. John Purcell

Tim Buchalka

Peggy Fisher

Rajeev Ratan

Amarnath Reddy

Ermin Kreponic

David Rombal

Keith Gebhardt

Professor Sean Carroll, Ph.D

Colt Steele

Jose Marcial Portilla

Machine Learning: Hands-On Python & R In Data Science.

Kirill Eremenko, Hadelin de Ponteves

Introduction to Computer Vision | Master OpenCV 3 in Python.

The Web Developer Bootcamp: HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, Node.js, MongoDB.

Oracle DBA 11q/12c - Database Administration for Junior DBA.

Thoughtful Web Development: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Vue.js, AJAX, PHP. OnlyKiosk Tech

Complete Ethical Hacking Course: SSL Strip, BruteForcing, DDoS, Reverse Shells.

The Complete Networking Fundamentals Course: Start your journey to CCNA.

Cisco Networking Fundamentals: Complete Cisco IT Networking Fundamentals course.

Mysteries of Modern Physics: Time. Professor Sean Carroll, Ph.D.

The Higgs Boson and Beyond.

Understanding Modern Electronics. Professor Richard Wolfson, Ph.D

Thermodynamics: Four Laws That Move the Universe. Professor Jeffrey C. Grossman, Ph.D

Ouantum Mechanics. Professor Benjamin Schumacher, Ph.D

Physics and Our Universe. Professor Richard Wolfson, Ph.D

Impossible: Physics Beyond the Edge. Professor Benjamin Schumacher, Ph.D

Black Holes, Tides, and Curved Spacetime: Understanding Gravity. Professor Benjamin Schumacher, Ph.D

Operating Systems

Windows 7/8/10, Mac OS X, iOS, Android, Debian, Linux Mint, Arch Linux, Raspbian, OpenWRT, Kali Linux, Parrot OS, Tails.

Linkedin in

For full and detailed information regarding my work experience, projects and awards please refer to my **Linkedin Profile**: it.linkedin.com/in/rambodrahmani.

GitHub 🗘

"Sharing isn't immoral it's a moral imperative. Only those blinded by greed would refuse to let a friend make a copy."

GitHub Profile: github.com/rambodrahmani.

Academia.edu 🏛

For full and detailed information regarding my personal studies please refer to my

Academia.edu Profile: pisa.academia.edu/ RambodRahmani.

Work Experience

2013 - 2016 **Presidency of the Council of Ministers - Department of Information for Security** Italy Italian Government - IT Analyst

I was recruited by Presidency of the Council of Ministers of Rome during the second semester of my first year at University of Pisa. I worked in several Italian cities for more than 2 years. I was involved in both software development and malware analysis for the Department of Information for Security.

2013 - 2016 **System Administrator**

Rambod Rahmani

I was involved in in-home Server Setup as part of our self-educating projects at EigenLab. Additionally I spent a great deal of time working on both dedicated servers and VPS (OS Installation, ISPConfig Setup and maintenance). The majority of my experiences as SysAdmin was focused on Linux Servers.

2014-2015 **Boccaccio Club**

Pisa. Italy

Software Programmer

Boccaccio Club iOS and Android App Development. Wireless Network Routing with Multiple Access Points: internet access is guaranteed only when the Boccaccio Club App is installed on your device. In order to achieve such an advanced authentication method I developed a custom captive portal named DYNAMO.

2015 PHOS Project

University of Pisa

Software Programmer

iOS and Android App development for PHOS Project (Aerospace project at University of Pisa part of the REXUS/BEXUS programme).

2013 Ciclope: Raspberry Pi based Humanoid

Rambod Rahmani, Giacomo Taormina

Software Development & Hardware Assembly

Ciclope is a Humanoid robot with the ability to see and analyse the external world using a camera. Its structure has up to 17 degrees of freedom.

It is a one-of-a-kind combination of Software and Hardware: it combines the latest OpenCV libraries and the RPi on board camera. I coded basic functionalities such as object-tracking and face-recognition, and its control interface using Python, C and C++.

2013 Ambulatory Proctology Office

Sardinia, Italy

Software Programmer

I developed a software named "Anamnesi" (Objective-C - MAC OS X) used to manage patients medical histories. Each patient is identified using his fiscal code and the ambulatory doctors are able to access all medical histories stored on a server wherever they are.

2012 **MALIBU Village**

Canet-Plage, Languedoc-Roussillon, France

Internship

I worked as IT Support at MALIBU Village as part of the "Leonardo Project" internship. This was the first time I had a hands-on experience with Ubiquiti Picostations.

2010 - 2012 Italian Navy

San Giorgio-class amphibious transport dock, Italy

Software Programmer

I coded a set of three software named **A.S.C** (Acceptance, Sorting and Control) for the Italian Navy. What started as a late night project to improve my coding skills ended up changing my life for ever when I was still a high school student. During more than two years of daily work I translated a NATO publication made in 2008 into machine language. Thanks to A.S.C. operators do not have to worry anymore about formatting and standardizing their messages: the software checks every line before sending the message and tells the operator how to correct any mistake.

OpenWRT 🛜

As a member of EigenLab, a local hacklab in Pisa, I was involved in installing and configuring the OpenWRT Distribution on embedded devices that we used to build EigenNet: a local **Wireless Mesh Network** in the city of Pisa.

Bitcoin B

I have been involved in Bitcoins as far as it regards Bitcoin Mining (CGMiner, CPUMiner, USB Miners), Mining Pools, Bitcoin Wallet and Full Bitcoin Node Configuration (Bitcoin Core).

Places 9

Iran, Italy, Germany, Spain, France, Belgium, Russia.

Last updated: September 16, 2017

Awards, Scholarships and Certificates

2013 - 2016 **DSU Scholarship** DSU of Tuscany DSU Scholarship by DSU of Tuscany supporting my Bachelor of Engineering

2013 - 2016 Italian Ministry of Education, University and Research Scholarship Excellence Scholarship by MIUR supporting my Bachelor of Engineering Studies.

2012 Intel Excellence in Computer Science Intel Corporation

Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software. **National Excellence Registry**

Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software.

2012

Certificate of Merit Scientific Lyceum "G. Spano", Italy Awarded to Rambod Rahmani for developing the A.S.C. Software.

Europass Mobility Nr. IT/00/2012/859/10

Gymnasium Lyceum "D. A. Azuni" and ALFMED (Académie de Langues France

Italian Ministry of Education, University and Research

Méditerranée.).

A.S.C. Software 2011 Italian Navy - San Giorgio-class Amphibious Transport Dock

Software Development Certificate by the Italian Navy for developing the A.S.C.

Software.

Studies.

Patents

2012

2012

2015 **DYNAMO** Ministry of Economic Development (Italy) - Request number: 102015000072776

> Captive portal software which allows for Wi-Fi Access Points to be configured so as to provide internet access only to those devices where a required iOS/Android App is installed. Otherwise the device only has internet access as far as it is needed to install the required App. I developed this custom Captive Portal in order to achieve the advanced authentication method required by Boccaccio Club and thanks to their financial support I was able to patent

DYNAMO.

Events

May 2015 **International World Wide Web Conference 2015** Florence, Italy Research, development, and applications of the topics related to the Web.

May 2015 **HEUREKA 2015** Berlin, Germany

One of the main founders conferences in the German--speaking world.

May 2015 **Berlin Talent Summit 2015** Berlin, Germany

Europe's leading recruiting conference for high-potentials.

9th EXPO-SCIENCES EUROPE 2012 (ESE) July 2012 Tula, Russia

9th MILSET Expo-Sciences Europe (ESE 2012) held in Tula, Russia.

April 2012 I Giovani E Le Scienze 2012 Federation of Scientific and Technical Associations

The A.S.C. Software was selected as one of the best 30 in the whole country.

nterests

Professional: Startup, Computer Science, Geolocation Systems, Hardware, Smartphones, iOS, Android, Embedded systems, Web development, App development, Software design, Networking, Linux, Hacking, Penetration Testing, Computational Complexity, Artificial Intelligence, Artificial Neural Networks, Computer Vision.

Personal: Running, Chess, Cosmology, Astronomical observations, Quantum Computer Science, Physics and Math.